listentoyourskin.org 2013-09-28

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy of Personally Identifiable Information
LEO Pharma Inc. (“LEO Pharma”) respects the privacy of visitors to the
www.Listentoyourskin.org website (the “Website”) and acknowledges that information
about you, your health, and your health care is sensitive. The term “personally
identifiable information” and “personal information” refers to information from which
you can be identified and includes your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail
address.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you how we may use personally
identifiable information or personal information collected from you when you visit the
Website and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and
correct, the information collected.
Consent
Use of this Website constitutes consent to data collection and use as described in this
Privacy Policy.
Collection of Data
There may be times when we ask you to provide certain personal information about
yourself, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc. We collect
only the personal information that you provide to us; therefore, in these situations, you
may choose to withhold any personal data requested. If you choose not to provide the
information we request, you may be unable to access certain services, offers, and content
on this Website.
The Website may use a technology known as “cookies”. The Website supplies your
browser with cookies, or tokens of information that contain a unique identifier and are
used for a variety of purposes, including remembering log-in information and providing
functionality to the Website. The cookies sent by the Website are used only by the
Website and are not used to collect personally identifiable information without your
permission. If you choose to furnish this Website with personally identifiable information
(such as your e-mail address), that information could be linked to the data stored in the
cookie. We reserve the right to change our use of cookies and our practices regarding
linkage to personally identifiable information without prior notification.
The Website also uses Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses. LEO Pharma may use your IP
Address to report aggregate information on use and to help improve the Website.
Generally, your IP Address is not linked with any personally identifiable information that
you provide. LEO Pharma, however, reserve the right to use IP Addresses to identify
users of the Website when necessary to enforce compliance with the Website’s terms and
conditions, or to protect the Website, its service, or other users.

Use of Data
LEO Pharma uses personal data for specific and limited purposes. For example, we may
collect and use personal data to provide you with products or services, to market products
and services that we think may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you via
email or regular mail for other purposes. . LEO Pharma will not sell, share, or otherwise
distribute your personally identifiable information to third-party individuals and entities
outside the LEO Group. However, personal data may occasionally be transferred to third
parties outside the LEO Group who act for, or on behalf of LEO Pharma, or in connection
with the business of LEO Pharma, for further processing in accordance with the purposes
for which the data was originally collected. Where disclosure of personal data to a third
party occurs for this purpose, we will endeavor to ensure that the processing of this data
is performed in accordance with the purposes and within the limits under which the data
was originally collected.
LEO Pharma will not treat as confidential any information that you provide that is not
personal or is not associated with any personally identifiable data, such as questions,
comments, or suggestions. LEO Pharma or another member of the LEO Group shall be
free to disclose and use this nonconfidential information for any purpose, without any
obligation whatsoever to you.
Protection of Children
LEO Pharma is committed to protecting the privacy of children. The Website does not
intend to collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years old
without the explicit consent of a parent or guardian.
Links to Other Websites
Any third-party websites linked to or from the Website may have different privacy
policies. When you access these external websites, the providers of the sites will have
access to certain information about you. You are encouraged to carefully review the
privacy policies of any other websites. LEO Pharma is not responsible for the privacy
practices or the content of any websites that we do not directly
control.
Updates
LEO Pharma reserves the right to change, modify, add or remove sections of this Privacy
Policy, in part or in whole.
1444742
